Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series VI: Project Files
  - Morris, Sarah - "Robert Towne - [Los Angeles]" - Drawing, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Rubins, Nancy - Site Plan, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - "The World is Round" - Poster, 2006-2007 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Shaun - "Wet Behind the Ear" bus shelter poster, 2008; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Alison Fleming bus shelter poster, 2008; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Brian Wengrf Skyx bus shelter poster, 2008; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Eric + Nadine bus shelter poster, 2008; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Poalo + Jason Pine bus shelter poster, 2008; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - "Griggs" [Yuma Project] - plans and drawings, undated (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Sonfist, Alan - watercolor, undated; 30 x 33 inches. (Flat-file-folder 2)
- Oversize Series VII: Press, Publications, and Promotional Material
  This series contains two oversize clear mock-ups of a Public Art Fund publication.
  - Public Art Fund Book Plates - 1 of 2, undated (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Public Art Fund Book Plates - 2 of 2, undated (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Oversize Series IX: Photographic Material
  Arranged chronologically, this series contains oversize photographic material pertaining to projects of the Public Art Fund.
  - "Ebbets Field at the Word Trade Center 1979" - [Brusk] (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Witz, Dan - "Sticks" Photographs, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Beecroft, Vanessa - Photograph, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Moore, Andrew - Photographs of City Hall, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - Mounted photograph, 2001; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Alÿs, Francis - "The Modern Procession" - Photographs, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Photographs, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Brosk, Jeffrey Owen - "Ebbets Field" - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - DiSuvero, Mark - Mounted Image, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Dubuffet, Jean -"La Chiffoniere" - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - General Project Images - Doris Freedman Plaza, undated (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Jerry - "Oceana" - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Katz, Alex - "Nine Women" - Mounted image - 1 of 2, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Katz, Alex - "Nine Women" - Mounted image - 2 of 2, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Martin, Knox - "Venus" - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Noguchi, Isamu - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Serra, Richard - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - [Smith, Tony] - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified project - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Wells, David - "Megagleaners on a Field Storefront Blue Chairs" - Mounted image, undated; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 6)